let questions = [
    {
        num: 1,
        question: "Who is the father of C language?",
        answer:" C. Dennis Ritchie",
        options: [
            " A. Steve Jobs",
            " B. James Gosling",
            " C. Dennis Ritchie",
            " D. Rasmus Lerdorf"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 2,
        question: "Which of the following does not represent a valid storage class in C?",
        answer: " A . Union",
        options: [
            " A . Union",
            " B . Static",
            " C . Extern",
            " D . Automatic"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 3,
        question: "When fopen() is not able to open a file, then it returns",
        answer: " C . Compiler Dependent",

        options: [
            " A . EOF",
            " B . NULL",
            " C . Compiler Dependent",
            " D . Runtime Error"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 4,
        question: "What will be x in the following c code? #include void main() {  int x; }",
        answer: " C . Integer Variable",

        options: [
            " A . Static Variable ",
            " B . Glabal Variable",
            " C . Integer Variable",
            " D . Registered Variable"
        ]
    },
    {
        num: 5,
        question: "According to ANSI specifications which is the correct way of declaring main when it receives command-line arguments?",
        answer: " C . Int main(int argc,char *argv[])",
        options: [
            " A . Int main {argc,argv)int argc; char *argv;",
            " B . Int main(){int argc ; char *argv);",
            " C . Int main(int argc,char *argv[])",
            " D . None"
        ]
    },
      {
        num: 6,
          question: "The operators . , !! , < , = if arranged in ascending order of precedence reads",
          answer: " A . =,!!,<,.",
        options: [
            " A . =,!!,<,.",
            " B . =,<,!!,.",
            " C . <,!!,=,.",
            " D . .,!!,<,="
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 7,
        question: "A pointer is a C which has not been initialized is know as:",
        answer: " B . Wild POinter",
        options: [
            " A . Far Pointer",
            " B . Wild POinter",
            " C . Void Pointer",
            " D . Null Pointer"
        ]
    },

    {
        num: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is not a standard C Library?",
        answer: " B . Retarg.h",
        options: [
            " A . Setjmp.h",
            " B . Retarg.h",
            " C . Signal.h",
            " D . Error.h"
        ]
    },
    // {
    //     num: 9,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     num: 10,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     num: 11,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     num: 12,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     num: 13,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },

    // {
    //     num: 14,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },
    // {
    //     num: 15,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },

    //   {
    //     num: 16,
    //     question: "What does HTML stands for?",
    //     options: [
    //         " A . Hyper Tesr la ",
    //         " B . Hyper Test Markup Language",
    //         " C . Hyper Test",
    //         " D . Hyper"
    //     ]
    // },
      
]